<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Jane - A simple theme for Hugo</title>
    <link>https://www.xianmin.org/hugo-theme-jane/categories/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Jane - A simple theme for Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 15:43:48 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.xianmin.org/hugo-theme-jane/categories/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>English Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://www.xianmin.org/hugo-theme-jane/post/english-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 15:43:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.xianmin.org/hugo-theme-jane/post/english-preview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is a very long title This is a very long title This is a very long title This is a very long title This is a very long title</title>
      <link>https://www.xianmin.org/hugo-theme-jane/post/this-is-a-very-long-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 15:43:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.xianmin.org/hugo-theme-jane/post/this-is-a-very-long-title/</guid>
      <description>This is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long titleThis is a very long title</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>